

### CONTACT



9655 South Las Vegas Blvd. Apt#: 269

Las Vegas , Nevada 89123 - 3393



702-670-8209



mlcvisualartist@gmail.com



www. mlcvisualartist.com

## EDUCATION



**The Illinois Institute of Art - Chicago**Chicago, Illinois 2006 - 2010

Bachelor's Degree:

Fine Arts in Media Arts & Animation



Oak Park & River Forest High School
Oak Park , Illinois 1997 - 2001
High School Diploma:

General Studies

## TECHNICAL SKILLS



Proficient and knowledgeable in computer platforms and software programs such as:































# MICHAEL L. CLARK

GRAPHIC DESIGN · ILLUSTRATION DESIGN · MUTLIMEDIA DESIGN

# RÉSUMÉ

## SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Over ten + years, educational and independent contractor | freelance work experience in Art Direction, Graphic Design, Illustration, Print, Animation and 3D Design. Strong understanding of pipeline in all mediums and capable of problem solving and communication individually or in team focused projects. Great attention to goals, details, organizational skills, creativity, enthusiasm, positive attitude and desire to approach projects with originality that serves to benefit any type of business.

## WORK EXPERIENCE



Upwork Santa Clara, California Independent Contractor : Graphic Artist (Remote)

Worked closely with a wide range | variety of clients | individuals, from different time zones in the United States of America. Clients include Trusted Exchange - A UPS Innovation, Studio Digital Fitness, Urban Amish, Sleep Better, Hike & Eat, Black Divinity, While They're Young, Little Rascals Child Care and many more. Projects include logo design, infographic design, advertising design, merchandise | fashion apparel design, image manipulation | collage design and illustration design.



Sunset Nights

Las Vegas, Nevada

Independent Contractor: Graphic Artist

Worked closely with the co-founder and producer on advertising layout designs for, social media promotion for music events, live-streaming on Twitch, for Covid -19 fundraiser.



Elite Sports of India - (ESI) (Formerly EFLI)

Pune, India & San Clemente , California (USA)

Independent Contractor: Graphic Artist (Remote)

Developed and collaborated with CEO, Co - CEO, director of operations and art | creative directors of ESI ( Elite Sports India) , EFLI ( Elite Foot Ball League of India) and EUSAI ( Elite Universal Sports Alliance of India ) - ESI Entities on development of team logo | branding and alternative uniform concept designs. Design mock - ups | modifications, merchandise | fashion apparel designs, store interior concept designs, basic interior floor plan designs, and formatting of digital files for international universities and sports leagues in India.



Elite Football League of India - (EFLI) ( Now ESI ) 2015 - 201

2020 - Present

2020

2016 - 2020

Pune, India & San Clemente , California (USA) Independent Contractor : Graphic Artist (Remotely)

Developed and collaborated with Co - CEO, director of operations and art directors of EFLI on development of team logo | branding concepts, alternative uniform concept designs, design mock - ups | modifications and formatting of digital files for international football leagues.

#### PAST WORK EXPERIENCE INCLUDES

















REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST